(Sheldon:)It doesn't matter what I want.
(Sheldon:)- It's your birthday. You decide.
- Oh, my God!
It's your birthday!
Let's do something fun.
(Amy:)- Uh...
- Well,
(Penny:)we could go to a bar.
(Scene:)Well...
(Leonard:)Okay, I can breathe again.
Babe, they want to have sex.
Oh, of course!
(Penny:)The annual birthday
booty spectacular!
(Sheldon:)That's a bit childish,
isn't it?
I'm sorry, and what flavor is
your bubble gum cigar?
(Sheldon:)Grape. I find it
the most mild.
(Penny:)All right, well,
you two go have fun.
(Leonard:)If we find my backup inhaler,
maybe we can get frisky.
(Penny:)Oh, you sexy,
wheezy little man.
(Bernadette:)Do you really need
to record this?
(Raj:)You'll be happy I did.
(Raj:)Okay, little one,
here we are back at home
(Raj:)because you weren't quite ready
to come out yet.
(Raj:)You wanted to make an entrance.
I get it.